{
    "subject": "resource/The_Legend_of_Bagger_Vance",
    "predicate": "ontology/musicComposer",
    "object": "resource/Rachel_Portman",
    "human_readable": "The music composer of The Legend of Bagger Vance is Rachel Portman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9576669335365295,
            "question": "Who composed the music for The Legend of Bagger Vance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8317744135856628,
            "question": "Who is the composer of The Legend of Bagger Vance's score?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.829312264919281,
            "question": "What type of work did Rachel Portman create for The Legend of Bagger Vance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8251521587371826,
            "question": "Rachel Portman composed music for which famous film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7683298587799072,
            "question": "What film features a soundtrack by Rachel Portman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7662115097045898,
            "question": "Is Rachel Portman a well-known musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6153898239135742,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that features Rachel Portman's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6050412654876709,
            "question": "What is Rachel Portman known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42934614419937134,
            "question": "Name a movie that Rachel Portman scored the music for."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15589271485805511,
            "question": "Can you name any other films that Rachel Portman has scored?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The music composer of The Legend of Bagger Vance is Rachel Portman.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5092_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a movie that Rachel Portman scored the music for.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5092_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Rachel Portman known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5092_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film that features Rachel Portman's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5092_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5092_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5092_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5092_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5092_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5092_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5092_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5092_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5092_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5092_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5092_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the soundtrack for \"The Legend of Bagger Vance\" and explicitly mention that Rachel Portman composed its music. Therefore, the triple stating that Rachel Portman is the music composer of \"The Legend of Bagger Vance\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}